ezlaptop.com 2003-10-01

# ezLaptop.com

**The following depicts the Privacy Policy of EZLaptop.com.**

Welcome to EZLaptop.Com's Privacy Policy. Keeping your privacy is very important to us here at EZLaptop.Com We will _never_ sell or give your personal information or e-mail to third-party companies. By reading our Privacy Policy and signing up on our site you are agreeing to our privacy policy, Thank you for visiting us, EZLaptop!

Information Collected

·         When placing an ordering on EZLaptop for the activation fee and eBook, you are submitting information to complete the transaction. All fields are required to complete your order. We only use this information to complete the transaction, and to keep our customers safe from credit card fraud. 

·         All information collected will never be shared with anyone else after the transaction is complete. 

·         Our main goal is to collect information for keeping our customers safe. 

·         You are able to browse our site without sending EZLaptop any personal information. Should you choose to use our services, you will be required to provide identity information, contact information, billing information, shipping information, e-mail information and other personal information as found on the forms within our site. This information also may be accessed by any kind of merchant account this is affiliated with EZLaptop.Com, such as PayPal.Com, and any other third-party merchant accounts we may use to process your order. 

Use of Your Information  

·         We use your information to complete the services you request. We may use your information to compare with other customers to find out if any customers are using multiple accounts, or aliases. 

·         You agree that we may use your information to improve our services. Again we will _not_ sell your information to third-parties in any way. 

Disclosure of Your Information  

·         Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot guarantee that your information will be only viewed by us at all times. We may have to disclose information to government if we are suspicious in any way of fraudulent activity going on with your account, or any other customers. 

Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information  

·         Should you need to review and change any personal information you have submit to us, you may contact us via e-mail to with the regular account that your name was signed up under.  By performing a request to make change of information, we will update your information ASAP. 

·         To make this request, email us. Such information will be asked: Have you received a new e-mail address? Have you received a new address? If so what is your new address? Do you have any new contact information such as name or telephone #? 

·         In the event of information changes, as you fail to notify us, will cause you to forfeit your eligibility for any free gifts you are signed up for in the matrix system. And no refunds will be provided. 

Security  
 ** **

·         EZLaptop.com uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. 

·         EZLaptop.com secured with protected against loss of information and unauthorized access.  We work have to guard all information's, however perfect security does not exist. 

Notice  
 ** **

·         We may update our privacy policy at any time. These updates will take effect immediately after posted. If one does not due so to agree with our privacy policy, you may be taken off the lists to receive your free gift. Along with no refunds will be provided. Please see our Terms of Service for any further details. 

By making a purchase, you agree to all terms of the Terms Of Service and Privacy Policy and any other policies described through out the EZLaptop.Com domain. By agreeing to all terms and conditions you loss any rights other than those listed above to have any expectation or action against EZLaptop.com employees or affiliates.
